ED]
Hello.
Hello. I'm Minami.
I am Sakura Kawasaki.
I am Rika Sato.
We just finished the Miyagi tour in Shinkoku-cho yesterday,
Where are you now?
Here we are in Iwate Prefecture.
Yay!
We've come all the way to Iwate.
I am so happy.
That's right. Speaking of Iwate.
Yes, Iwate is where I am from. I, Rika Sato, was born there.
That's right.
Thank you very much.
Do you do much filming in your hometown?
Not really.
I didn't get a chance to go down with all the members like this very often,
I was very happy and looking forward to it.
You can see it in the background, but it's pretty amazing.
The view.
It's a little too bright to open my eyes.
Yes, it is. It's dazzling.
What's this place?
It's called Genbikei, where you can see a spectacular view,
There is also a famous dumpling called "dressed dango," which flies in the sky.
What? What do you mean?
They are really flying in the sky, and when you put money in the dumpling and give a signal, the dumpling flies up from the other side of the river,
When you put money in and give a signal, the dumplings come to you from the other side of the river using a rope.
They call them flying dumplings because they come from the other side of the river using a rope.
That's right.
I want to see it. Can I see it? It's over there.
It's right there. You might be able to see it.
In Rika's hometown,
Rika's hometown.
Let's see.Uh...
It's different.
It's in Rika-chan's hometown, isn't it?
What shall we eat at the national tour in Iwate?
Yay!
Wait. Wait a minute.
That's it. That's it.
I only saw the loop.
You only saw the loop, right?
Because the dumplings came a little bit during the title call,
I'm waiting,
Rika-chan's hometown is where she's from,
What shall we eat on the national tour in Iwate?
Yay!
So, are we going to Rika-chan's recommended restaurant today?
Yes, we are going to a restaurant recommended by Rika-chan. I asked my mom for her recommendation,
She wrote me a letter and I would like to read it today.
That's kind of nice.
First of all, there were so many recommendations that I got lost,
Let me introduce Mr. Ushiko Ogata.
Ogata-san is owned by a ranching company,
They serve high quality meat at a reasonable price.
They have a set of meat called "Gyu-Ko-O",
Please enjoy the delicious meat at Yakiniku.
It's a pleasure!
It's a great yakiniku.
Yakiniku!
I'm so glad.
So they're going to write on the board.
I will write. I'll write.
Beef small tail.
What kind of set is it?
I'm looking forward to it.
Then! Here it is.Then! Here it is.
We came near Iwate on a tour,
Ushiko Ogata's Ushiko Ori.
K.Y.!
Yay!
There it is.
That's it!
Shall we go? Mr. Ogata.
Let's go.
Have you been there before, Mr. Ogata? Rika-chan?
I haven't,
I knew it was a very famous restaurant in my hometown,
I've always wanted to go there.
Just like that.
I'm so happy.
I'm happy. Me too.
First time for all of us.
First time.
Is it too hot?
It's too hot. It's not good.
I found something.
It's true. I found Sakutan.
What is it?
What! It looks like we've arrived.
Yay!
Wow! What's going on?
There's something here.
There is a cow.
Amazing.
Here they come.
Yay!
This is amazing.
This is what Rika-chan's mother recommended.Here's the one Rika's mom recommended.
Beef Potion Molly
Looks delicious!
Shall we order this?
This and...
I want vegetables!
I wonder if it's okay... how am I supposed to eat this?
I wonder if it's okay.
Do you think it's okay?
I want to eat kimchi if there is any
Looks delicious
Colorful
There's kimchi with Chinese cabbage, and it's got horny enemies.
Beef chops and this.
That's it.
And this.
This one.
this
What did you eat recently?
Oh!
Chorigi salad!
I want chorigi salad.
I want to eat it digitally.
Let's eat it!
I don't have a recommendation one digital.
Yes, I do.
What's in the recommended digital?
There's a thing called recommended one digital.There's this one digital thing I recommend.
It's true.
Maybe there's a blooming tan in there.
There's kimchi.
Good, I recommend it.
You don't have to ask me about this one.
Take care of it.
I'll take care of it.
You too, sir.
Yes, ma'am.
Do you recommend the choreggi salad?
I recommend it.
Thank you.
It's become popular.
I'm glad.
Chorégi-Salad is also very popular.
Thank you very much
Please do me a favor.
I go out to eat with the members.
Oh, I go sometimes.
The last time I went was with Youmekinao or
I ate Italian food with Tanaka Sayu.
How stylish!
We did.
But you know a lot about cars, don't you, Umeyama-san?
I also go out to eat yakiniku quite a bit.
I go out to eat with Kaede Sato and Kaede a lot.
What do you order?
I love raw meat.
I love yukke and beef tongue.
Beef tongue is delicious!
That's why I was so happy at last night's show.
It's delicious, isn't it?
Oh, here it is!
Wow!Wow.
It's amazing.
Looks delicious.
Oh, man.
Looks delicious
Thank you so much.
Looks so delicious.
ribs over and over
kaburi kaburi
Not ribs, but kaburi
kaburi
fresh
never heard of it
tata san kaku
We have wasabi, so here is the name of wasabi
We have wooden soy sauce, so here is the name of the soy sauce and here is the name of the soy sauce
We also have grilled meat
We also have some sea salt and seaweed from the sea in the city of Aichi Prefecture.
Please enjoy it as well!
Thank you very much.
Looks delicious!
Oh, wow... the kimchi you ordered.
Kimchi!
Kimchi looks delicious!
Amazing!
I'll start with the ones that have oil on them.
I'll start with the ribs.
Bite into it!
Wow!
Good work, everyone!
Thank you for your hard work!
kabuli, not kalbi, kabuli.
Interesting.
Cholgi salad is here.
Chorgi SaladCholgi Salad
Cholgi Salad is also here!
Chorgi Salad.
I like it.
It's interesting.
345 regulations.
Me too?
It's so arrachio!
I was so surprised... it's so different from what I imagined.
I love salt.
I'll start with the salad.
Shall we eat?
Bon appétit!
Choreggi salad is delicious!
It's so good!
It's my favorite salad.
I know... it's perfect with grilled meat.
Okay, okay.
Looks good.
Thank you so much.
Thank you very much.
All right.
Who do you want to eat first?
Mr. Umeyama?
No, no, no, no, no, no, not before.
No, no, no, I knew it.
Bon appétit.
Looks delicious.
Yeah. Soft across the sponge.
Soft. So cute.
Soft like a sponge. It's so soft, it's delicious.
Good. How's the browning?
It's very, very good. Very, very good.
It's so good. Thank you very much.
Oh, wow. It's got a nice oil on it.Wow, wow, it's got good oil on it.
Visual. Yay!
Mmm!
Ooh!
Looks good!
Ugh...
It's too good.
Eh, okay.
It soaks up the fat.
It's kind of wasabi soy sauce.
It's surprisingly refreshing.
There's fat, too, but...
It's true, it's true.
Delicious!
It goes well with it.
I'll have it.
I think I'll have the salt.
Longing? It's my dream.
You've never been here before.
And the road here...
I've been driving by it a lot.
I've been looking at it, thinking how nice it is.
It's so big!
It's big, isn't it?
It's a big one.
Bon appétit!
Mmm!
Is it good?
It's so good!
Oh, good!
It's like fresh chocolate.
We're not the same, but the sponge and the chocolate are totally different.
It's so soft.
Delicious!Delicious.
Good. It's delicious.
It's like a high quality meat.
Yes, because it's like this.
Wow!
Let's grill some more.
I just remembered a girl I often go out with.
Sakurabaka-san is good friends with a girl named Kira Matsumoto.
Whenever we meet up with her, we always go out for yakiniku.
I see. She's very funny, isn't she?
Very funny.
I recorded the show, too, Mr. Sakurabaka.
You're so funny!
She's so funny!
I always leave laughing.
You feel the same as usual?
He's the same, really.
And he's always like that.
Thank you very much.
Looks delicious. Fresh.
Fresh.
Bon appétit!
Delicious.
Mmm!
Mmm. Yum. Yum.
Delicious.
It's less fatty than before.
I can feel the meat all over.
The taste of meat.
It's delicious.
Yes, it is.
It's good.
It's good. I like it.I love it! I love it! I love it!
I like it! I had it!
I like it. - I like it. - I like it.
You like it leaner?
No, I like the fatty side.
I like ribs.
But I used to be a big fan of ribs.
Maybe I'm getting old... or maybe it's the potato sores.
Five. Five.
Hey, Banalo!
Bon appétit!
Mmm!
Oh, my God, it tastes like meat.
- Cute. Tastes like meat. Cute. Cute.
I want to keep it fresh.
- Okay? You should try it.
- It's delicious. Thank you.
Too many funny comments, huh?
- Just the other day, Satsuki and the Cat Tongue Showroom.
- Yes, that's right.
- We were talking about how she'd be the best.
If I had a sister like Ms. Umezawa, she'd be the best.
- I saw that.
- Did you see it? Did you see it? I'm so happy.
I'm so proud of you.
I want to be proud of you.
- Not at all.
- Saki is your sister?
- She's sandwiched between a sister and an older brother.
- Yeah, she's the middle child.
Are they close?
- Siblings get along great.
My siblings get along great. My sister and I get along great.
We go to a lot of places together.
- You're a year apart?
- We're a little older.- They're a little older than me.
They're too cute to fight, and they've never had a fight.
- He's too cute.
- Not even with my brother.
- I see.
- So we're pretty close.
They get along pretty well... and listen to their older brother's voice.
- He's too cute. He's too nice.
Why are you so firm, Mr. Umezawa?
- I'm really not.
I just hide it.
But I think you're both solid.
- What? Not at all.
- I don't think that's easy to convey.
I think there's more to them than meets the eye.
So I thought your fans might be a little confused.
I think you're both so solid.
- Well, I've never thought of you as solid.
- Yeah.
- I'm glad.
- Thank you for dinner.
- That was delicious.
- It was delicious.
- Yes, so we had a delicious meal at Kogata-san's.
We had a delicious meal at Ogata-san's.
Actually, there's one more thing...
- Yes, another one's coming.
- It seems it's arrived.
- The other recommended restaurant is Japanese Restaurant Shochiku.
Originally a long-established eel restaurant with a 100-year history.
I recommend the Sauce Katsudon.
The cutlet is crispy and the sauce is delicious!
You can choose between "loin cutlet" and "filet cutlet".
For those who want to eat both
I recommend the "Katsu-don" lunch set which has one loin cutlet and one filet cutlet on top.
I recommend the Katsu-don Lunch Set which has one loin cutlet and one filet cutlet.We recommend the Katsu-don lunch set!
Since you have come all the way to Iwate
I want you to taste a lot of delicious food!
- Katsudon.
- Katsudon?
- Katsudon? Katsudon?
- Filet and?
- Filet and loin cutlet.
- Looks delicious.
- One each.
- Gorgeous, isn't it?
- Gorgeous.
Let's be carnivorous girls today.
- Carnivore.
- Am I right?
- Yeah, it fits.
- Yes, it is. - Good.
We're in Iwate on tour.
Shotake-san's katsudon style.
- Yay!
- Let's go.
- Ta-da!
- Let's go!
We're on our way to Sho-take-san's.
- We're on our way.
- This is great. Is this right in front of the station?
- Yes, it's right in front of the station.
- Oh, here it is.
- Here it is.
- Here he is.
- Gallynn!
- What a nice store!
- Yes, it is.
It's a Japanese restaurant.
- Let's go there.
Thank you for watching.Thank you for watching.
The one you were talking about earlier?
Yes, this is it.
It's the Okiji Aburi lunch menu that you can order at night.
I see.
I'd like three items from the lunch menu, please.
Yes, please.
Sauce?
Yes, it's called "Sauce Katsudon".
It's a famous local restaurant.
I like that you can have both the loin and the filet.
It's good, isn't it? One piece at a time.
I love teishoku-ya like this.
I like it. The lighting is really stylish.
It's nice.
Hot.
It's hot.
Very hot!
It's hot in Iwate.
Hot?
Very hot, very hot.
I see.
It seems to be one of the hottest places in Japan.
I see it on the news sometimes.
Really?
I thought it was supposed to be cooler.
Yes, it is in Tohoku, isn't it?
But I feel like I'm on a little trip today!
That's true.
Are there really that many kids from out of town?
I often go to Yokohama Arena in Kanagawa.
I've been to live shows there.
But you don't say, "I'm home.
That's right.
That's true. It's hard.
I'm jealous.I envy you.
Everyone says "I'm home" in their own dialect.
I'm back!" or "I'm back!
I can't do anything.
but I can't do anything!
But I hear there are lots of sightseeing spots...
Enoshima, Kamakura...
Enoshima, Enoshima, Kanagawa.
But you can't say that's your hometown, either.
It's not really local.
That's right.
But I went sightseeing in Enoshima.
Really?
By myself.
Nice. Alone?
Alone.
I wanted to see the ocean.
So I took the train.
The Enoden is nice, isn't it?
The Enoden was great.
Bon appétit!
Gachidekko!
Thank you so much!
Amazing.
So many!
Oh, I'm going to have some.
You want some?
The moment they open...
You want to take a picture of it, don't you?
It's open!
Bon appétit!
Here we go.
Wow!
Looks good. Hot, hot, hot.
Looks good. Two kinds. Let's try them.
Yum, yum. It's big. Thank you. Can I eat it? Can I eat it? I'm going to eat it. Please eat it.It looks delicious. It's huge. Thank you. Can I eat it? I'm going to eat it. Please eat it.
Mmm! It's a loin, for sure! This is the loin!
Yum!
Crispy batter.
It looks so delicious!
I'll have some too.
Bon appétit!
Yeah, it's so crispy and delicious!
Yeah, it's soaked in flavor.
It's soaked up all the flavor.
It's not too much of a good set meal. It's too nice.
Miso soup, pickles, orange salad, tomatoes.
Lots of kobachi.
It's a nice lunch. The weather's really nice.
It's a nice lunch, the weather's really nice.
I'm glad we're from such different places.
I'm glad we're here.
I'm also happy to be here.
I'm glad.
We did an album the year before last.
We went around for a local campaign, right?
But I stayed overnight. Where did you go then?
I was in Nagoya. Nagoya.
With Saku and Ikuta.
You were doing the Consume Dance, right?
That was a lot of fun, too.
I'd like to go somewhere with everyone.
I'd love to go.
I don't remember any album campaigns for the first term.
We've never done that. That's right.
At the beginning...
We went to different places in different prefectures.
We'd go to shopping malls and shake hands.
I'd like to go to shopping malls and shake hands.
I'd like to do something like that. It'd be fun.
I'd like to go to Nissan live concerts and stuff like that.From the very beginning, the first term students have been doing Nissan Live or something like that.
or something like that.
I'd like to do something like that.
It's true that it was the first time
Nissan?
Isn't that amazing?
I was shaking.
I had my orientation in April.
Most of the girls had theirs in February.
You were ahead of me.
Mr. Umezawa...
at my first omiai meeting.
I felt very comfortable with him.
I felt so relieved.
Mr. Manatsu and I had a surprise for you.
The self-introduction of Sakudan was too funny
We did it in a roundabout way.
It was really just that moment
I thought she was a little bit crazy.
In a good way.
She did it with a normal face.
It was really funny.
That's what stuck out to me the most.
This is your second year, right?
It's my second year.
Rika, it's your fourth year.
This is my fourth year.
We have to work hard.
That's right.
I never really...
Until last year.
I didn't have time to look around.
But this year, I'm starting to look around a little more.
And when I see the third term students enjoying each other's company
I see them enjoying each other's company.When I see you enjoying yourself.
It makes me really happy.
The third term students are really noisy, aren't they?
Not at all.
Mmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmm mmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmm
The rice is so bad.
Rice is delicious.
Himehime
Thank you for the food
So today
I visited two places and had a meal...
How was it?
It was great to be able to introduce you all to the delicious food of Iwate, my home prefecture.
I got to eat with my seniors and juniors.
We had a great time eating together with my seniors and juniors.
It was weird.
I hope you all had a great time!
Please go there!
It's a very famous restaurant in Iwate Prefecture
I heard it's a very famous restaurant in Iwate Prefecture.
Rika's mother went out of her way
Rika's mother took the trouble to tell me about it, and I was so happy to be able to go there.
I was so happy to be able to go there and
and the food was so delicious!
All in all
I can go home with a happy feeling.
Thank you very much.
You really showed me around.
This is the last in our series on local cuisine.
We're the last in this series.